[Music]
are you sure we're going the right way
big blue
i don't feel safe in this neighborhood
yeah beach i heard this part of town is
filled with predominantly mexicans let's
locate your friend before another
drive-by starts with another one of
those bouncing cars
look there he is
see i told you we were going the right
way
damn that [ __ ] stinks like [ __ ]
trevor hey how's it going there buddy
sonic you actually came did you have
trouble finding the house
oh i didn't i didn't ask you brought
your friends with you
is that bad
no it's it's fine
i'm glad you're all here to tell you the
truth if i'm being honest tonic i didn't
even think you would shop yourself
of course i would trevor you're my buddy
wait i'm your i'm your best friend
uh well i don't know if i would go that
far
i would
anyhow i just got done throwing out the
poop sack so let's go inside
hold on did this [ __ ] just say poop
sack
the town turn off my plumbing because i
couldn't keep up with the bills i poop
in bags because it helps me save up
money no other reason doesn't it stink
sometimes but now i put in the freezer
next to the ice trays that way you are
unable to smell as much throughout the
house trevor my family owns this section
of town i know you haven't missed a
single bill if it's your fetish you can
say so we're all guys here nobody will
judge you
come on inside now we can start the
party
hey trevor are you ready to look my
dirty butthole
say hi pals cyrus got here just before
you did
um hi what's up i really really didn't
expect to see anybody else here today
in fact i was led to believe that it was
just going to be the two of us
cyrus i told you to shut the [ __ ] up and
my other friends arrived you're going to
make me look bad
you know i only keep you around for some
cheap ass as a matter of fact make
yourself useful and lose the pantaloons
give daddy some eye candy
trevor cyrus are you guys homosexuals
what in the world would even give you
the idea
but these guys are our guests so we have
to treat them as such
go in the kitchen and get them some
drumstick ice creams i will make it up
to you some other day [ __ ]
trust me dude you're gonna love these
things
i can shove them in my butt they're so
good
oh god damn it
trevor one of your disgusting poop sacks
door open again
just push it to the back and don't let
knuckles see it i mean he already saw
it's leaking everywhere
did i tell you to explain to me what it
looks like [ __ ] just shove in the
corner and i will throw it away tomorrow
ah [ __ ]
oh well at least the ice cream is okay
here knuckles take this only a little
bit of trevor's diarrhea got onto this
one
no thanks i think i'll pass
you can just go ahead and shove it up
everybody get down there's another drive
by going on outside
you sure took your time did you bring me
my ice cream
right here daddy do i get my reward now
oh you'll get it all right tonight after
everybody else has gone home
oh baby are you going to look at my
butthole
i was thinking more along the line of
plane checkers i guess we can do both if
you
want so you're knuckles the echidna we
haven't gotten the chance to formally
meet like this i'm sure sonic talks
about me quite a bit to his other
friends
no he doesn't actually
he doesn't that's strange me and him go
way back
is it true that you're a hippie
yes i am
i'm not going to shake your hand
that's fine by me
i didn't want to shake yours anyway
manic i refuse to stay in this house any
longer
call you mom and tell her to pick us up
what's the rush
we still didn't even have dinner yet
you can't be serious i've been here for
two minutes and i already got people
trying to pop some caps in my ass i'm
going to be picking glass shards from my
ass for weeks
knuckles the echidna is right manic
maybe maybe we shouldn't have come here
after all
trevor's house is too scary and too
dangerous
even more so than the planet movies when
the evil doctor robotnik ruled over it
like an evil dictator
no i'm not sonic why are you saying such
things weren't you my friend
bro give me the phone i'm calling mommy
are you happy now retired you got what
you wanted
you bet
now bend over that ass belongs to me
no i do not consent to this
too bad for you i don't even know what
that word means
[Music]
hello this is sonya speaking
who is this and why the hell are you
calling my mom
sonia why do you have mom's cell phone
she went out to buy popcorn so she left
it for me in case of an emergency
i'm watching harry potter with uncle
chuck and the girls it's not going very
well though the only one who seems to be
enjoying himself is uncle chuck but i
don't really know why
when are you and manic coming home
mom said we can't start dinner until
everyone's at the table
well the thing is it turns out trevor
lives in one of you know those
neighborhoods
we can't exactly just walk home since
it's getting kind of late
oh [ __ ] well i hope you don't die
sonia may i use the phone i need a
moment from all this black magic talk
okay but after that can you please leave
my house
hi it's this sonic i was just wondering
is it true that you are gay and that you
let bartleby spank you all yes
ah yeah why do you ask
i only wanted to let you know that i
might not agree with your lifestyle but
please know that i won't judge you
well you won't
thanks
although it's 2021 now so homophobia
doesn't really exist anymore
we all have to face our evil sins
eventually and i am sure you'll get
what's coming to you someday
[Music]
change of plans boys we re not going
home after all
really you're staying all right i'll
show you just how fun and cool i can be
how about some board games we can order
some little c-series pizza and play
candyland
what do you say beach sounds like a
swell time i know how much you like
candy land i'll even let you have a
yellow pea
well i do like candy land
great the board games in the attic come
on sonic let's go get well everyone else
stays down here for the pizza guy
wow it smells so clean
yeah i keep most of my poop sacks
downstairs on the first floor
wait right here sonic i'm going to check
over on that side and don't touch
anything unless i say so
you got it don't take too long it's
pretty spooky up here haha
[Music]
what the what's that over there
looks like a book
oh boy i wonder if it's a cookbook for
chili dogs
or bushes baked beans
up a book on kidnapping and abduction
what a strange book
why on earth would someone like trevor
have something like this playing around
in the attic
oh sonic weren't you listening to me
when i said not to touch anything
if you're so curious why don't you come
over here with me
i think i found candyland and i'm not
just talking about the board game
but the real deal you fat i know you'll
like that [ __ ]
trevor i don't like it up here
can we please go back downstairs
the others are waiting
in a minute first come help me with this
box of board games they are too heavy
for me along
trevor what are you talking about
there's nothing in here it's just an
empty crate not for long
trevor why
trevor what is the meaning of this
let me outright this instant
this isn't funny
you are not going anywhere sonic you are
going to be my friend forever and ever
we are going to eat ice cream
and watch movies together but first i
need to kill your green brother so he
does figure out my plans
no you leave my family out of this you
bastard
so you want to play it rough that's fine
by me i have all night to gain your
obedience
let's see if you're willing to talk more
after an hour in the dark
unbelievable is that what i think it is
hey i remember these toys i played with
these when i was just a kid it's been so
long
[Music]
i'm so glad trevor likes his new rattle
baby i told you he would like it
and all it cost was two dollars at
goodwill
i can't believe someone just gave it
away
i don't give a [ __ ]
just give your husband some sugar before
i go down to the bar to watch the game
damn it trevor [ __ ] in his [ __ ] baby
pants again what a dumb poopy baby
go change himself before it makes the
room smell like beef and broccoli
you do it bro i did it the past 138
times
it's about time you put some effort into
this marriage for a change
what did you say you [ __ ]
say that again
okay
it's about time you put some effort in
you think you control me
you are a woman
and women are [ __ ]
[Music]
that is enough
i am your sister and your wife i will
not stand for this
okay then sit down
either way i'm beating your ass
shut up
all you do is poop and cry
you're already two years old when are
you going to learn you can't keep doing
that
what are you doing get your paws off of
me you feel fear inch
this poo poo boy is my prey this isn't
fair you told me it would be my turn to
beat the baby the next time he acts up
why are you always lying to me does the
sweating ring mean nothing to you my own
bro
trevor stop running no don't run outside
there's a drive-by going on out there
[ __ ] babe trevor got caught up in a
drive-by again
go get some band-aids
hey boys i got the board game who's
ready to play
i kyle first did on the yellow piece
up where is my bro
didn't he go up in the attic with you
yeah and when is the pizza guy supposed
to show up i'm starting to think he's
not coming
yeah where is my beach little man i do
want to know right now or i will hit you
with my massive swinging balls that way
87 pounds
oh you mean sonic as in sonic the
hedgehog
he went home
what did you say you let him go alone in
a neighborhood like this how foolish
what if he runs into someone who is not
white
i'm sorry he just seemed really eager to
get home to play roblox
[ __ ]
bart levy you can't go it's almost 8 p.m
it's too dangerous what if you get shot
at
you do realize i'm not lb
stop right there kid well have you taken
my [ __ ]
help help me can anybody hear me bart
levy please i'm so frightened
it's no use nobody can hear me what am i
going to do now
am i sonic the hedgehog really trapped
in this domain until the end of time
who is that is somebody out there daddy
is that you did you come back for me
that voice is someone out there
i'm in a box where are you are you here
to save me
we seem to be in a similar situation
kate
how would you end up here
but that sold me to some dude named
trevor for a bag of fun yums and a case
of beer i got the last laugh though
because i stole the funyums and kicked
my dead in the balls before he locked me
in here
why did trevor by you
cause i got a thick ass he couldn't keep
his eyes off it
damn how old are you
i am three years old
did you try calling the police
i couldn't because they put me in a box
now stop talking and let me eat my fun
yams oh man this sucks and i gotta fart
now too
oh well when you gotta let one loose
there's no stopping it
[Music]
that freight runs i recognize it but how
can this be
is my boy still back at the house
why didn't you just tell me at first
that you didn't kidnap my [ __ ]
i did
but you called me gay and punched me in
the face
hang tight my love daddy is coming to
rescue your
oh osiris you better watch out you don't
want to get stuck in the peppermint
first again
what's gonna happen if i do are you
gonna slip a peppermint stick between my
ass cheeks
did you guys hear that what the hell was
that it sounded like some massive thing
exploded
i didn't hear anything i'm sure you're
just imagining it
it sounds like it came from the attic do
you think somebody broke in i'm sure
it's nothing let's get back to the game
knuckles is right trevor we can't afford
to sit around and find out let's go
upstairs
i have to do something in fast if those
to find out what's in the attic i'm
through
it's fine trevor even if somebody did
reagan you and me can just rape him
wait trevor what are you doing put that
think away oh wait is this some sexual
role play damn you're one kinky son of a
[ __ ]
everybody drop your pants i'm gonna [ __ ]
you
it took me 213 days but i finally got
you [ __ ]
why why is this happening all i wanted
was friends
all i wanted was people to spend time
with it's not fair
sonic why is it that you get to have so
many friends and not me
is it because i'm ugly is that why
yeah what do i get my parents were
killed when i was just a baby you have a
mother and siblings and the most
beautiful boyfriend in the whole world
growing up everybody picked on me in
school because my parents were siblings
and people thought that was weird for
some reason
that's enough trevor you've said enough
i'm not angry with you
really you're not bad
no i'm not
trevor if you wanted to hang out all you
had to do was ask really but i thought
you hated me and that's why you never
hung out with me because i was weird and
my parents are sublings there's a lot of
reasons why i don't hang out with you
trevor but that's not why
it's okay kid my parents are siblings
too
yeah and so are mine well sonic i was
always jealous of you but now i realize
why you have so many friends it's
because you're so so nice i wonder if
everyone was like you would the worldly
more beautiful place
hey everybody the pizza is finally here
oh [ __ ] did he say pizza
i ordered a five dollar hot and ready
pizza from little c serves that we could
all split i understand if you don't want
to stay anymore
stay here
trevor do you even gotta ask we are all
bros bros gotta stick together
you see now trevor you don't need to try
so hard with friendship
sometimes just being a good guy goes a
long way
everyone i don't know how to thank you
well you could start by dividing up that
pizza
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
welcome everyone to the first official
fan gathering
of the anti-sonic underground fan club
i'm happy to see so many of you i hope
you didn't have much trouble getting
here with all those su fans wandering
about
yeah
why don't you just cut to the chase and
explain why you called to look us
together are we going to kill sonic
are we going to make our move today or
what i'm tired of sitting on my fat ass
can't we just go curd stomp that fat
blue hedgehog right now
settle down robbie rotten i promise that
time will come and so much more but
first i need to make a few things clear
now that we're all together under one
roof
you call yourselves a team the new boys
as a matter of fact
but i don't see that
actually i see [ __ ] my [ __ ]
the truth is that you pale in comparison
to the original boys that once fought
the sonic underground
but it's not too late
what you guys need is order it needs a
real leader but it's not too late what
you guys need is order it needs a real
leader
and that's why i'm here i'm the leader
me randy the next door neighbor to the
hedgehog family
you think people will serve under you
when you're not as sexy as me you're
nothing
nobody
that's funny because i just so happen to
be a member of the japanese yakuza
oh my god
that's right
if you want to fight the sonic
underground you're going to need an army
we all hate sonic underground and the
world would be better off without it
we can all agree to that i'm sure
this is a once in a lifetime offer i am
giving you
and all i ask in return is the position
of leader sounds like a fear or
trade-off if you ask me
i become the leader of the new boys and
you get the accuses 8 in battle
and at the days and sonic underground
will be finished
you want to know what i think here's
what i think about your leadership
the only one strong enough to take out
sonic underground is me
you big doo doo head
[Music]
that's what i think of your gay offer
let's let him have it boys
[Music]
[Applause]
this is what you get for always being a
thorny my ass
[Music]
randy spider-man betrayed us
he's helping the enemy
[ __ ] hurry
everybody fart on spider-man
don't let him get away with this
[Music]
all right now that that's over and done
with who wants to go out for burgers
i got to some coupons for free small
fries with every purchase
after that we'll go kill bartleby's
[ __ ] sonic with a gun
i'm crazy
and i thought my jokes were bad
give me one good reason why i shouldn't
have my boy here pull your head off
how about a magic trick i'm going to
make this pencil disappear
up someone's ass
[Applause]
[Music]
tada
it's
god oh and by the way this suit it
wasn't cheap you ought to know you
bought it [ __ ]
the [ __ ] you saved me
wait randy don't shoot him
i think we should at least hear his
proposition first
now let's wind the clocks back i won't
dare cross any of you i mean what
happened did your boss drop off you see
a guy like me
a freak
look listen i know why you guys choose
to have your little group therapy
sessions out in broad daylight i know
why you're afraid to go out or not
bodily you see
bottlebee he's shown the world your true
colors unfortunately
the failure of the original boys
that was only the beginning up in this
[ __ ]
and as your plans from going forward
bobby don't give a [ __ ] what you do
he'll find one of you he'll make you
squeal like a [ __ ] and i know the
squeal is when i see them
then what do you propose
it's simple
we destroy the sonic underground
if it's so simple then why haven't you
done it already [ __ ]
if you're good at something never do it
for free
how much do you want half
you're crazy
look if we don't deal with this now soon
little randy here won't be able to even
buy another belt to whip his son with
that's it enough from the clown
let's not blow things out of proportion
oh my god
he's got a bum sticking out of his crack
why you you think you can just steal
from us and walk away
yeah
i'm putting the word out
500 000 for this clown dead a million
alive
so i can't fight him look if you if you
change your mind just give me a call
here's my cow [ __ ]
[Music]
that damn clown who does that guy think
he is playing us like fools
i can't wait to poopy in his butt and
then make him eat it
hello is this the place for the
antisonic underground fangled meet up
i seriously hope i'm not too late oh no
you're right on time we're glad to have
you do you hate sonic underground also
something like that i have a sneaking
suspicion that a person i am currently
tracking
or working with them
a suspicious person
what are you some kind of detective
you can call me a detective of sorts you
wouldn't be too far off
tell us who that is who is it who are
you looking for
hero
you